const exprssionsOperators = [
  {
    question: "What is the result of the expression '5 + 3 * 2' in JavaScript?",
    options: ["16", "11", "26", "Error"],
    correctAnswer: "11",
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used for exponentiation in JavaScript?",
    options: ["**", "^", "^^", "ex"],
    correctAnswer: "**",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'typeof' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "To check if a variable is defined",
      "To determine the type of a variable",
      "To convert a variable to a string",
      "To check if a variable is null",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To determine the type of a variable",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the '++' operator do in JavaScript?",
    options: ["Increments a variable by 1", "Decrements a variable by 1", "Doubles the value of a variable", "Negates the value of a variable"],
    correctAnswer: "Increments a variable by 1",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a comparison operator in JavaScript?",
    options: ["&", "==", "+", "!"],
    correctAnswer: "==",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the '!=='' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "Checks for strict equality",
      "Checks for inequality with type coercion",
      "Checks for strict inequality",
      "Checks for equality with type coercion",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Checks for strict inequality",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the '||' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: ["Logical AND", "Logical OR", "Bitwise OR", "Bitwise AND"],
    correctAnswer: "Logical OR",
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used to find the remainder of a division in JavaScript?",
    options: ["%", "&", "/%", "rem"],
    correctAnswer: "%",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the '?:' ternary operator in JavaScript?",
    options: ["Conditional assignment", "Logical OR", "Bitwise AND", "Logical XOR"],
    correctAnswer: "Conditional assignment",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'typeof NaN' return in JavaScript?",
    options: ["'number'", "'undefined'", "'string'", "'NaN'"],
    correctAnswer: "'number'",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'delete' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: ["To remove a property from an object", "To delete a variable", "To delete a function", "To delete a file from the server"],
    correctAnswer: "To remove a property from an object",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'void' operator do in JavaScript?",
    options: ["Returns undefined", "Throws an error", "Performs a bitwise NOT operation", "Evaluates an expression"],
    correctAnswer: "Returns undefined",
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used for string concatenation in JavaScript?",
    options: ["+", "-", "*", "/"],
    correctAnswer: "+",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'in' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "Checks if a property exists in an object",
      "Performs arithmetic addition",
      "Checks if a variable is null",
      "Performs bitwise AND operation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Checks if a property exists in an object",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'typeof undefined' return in JavaScript?",
    options: ["'undefined'", "'null'", "'object'", "'string'"],
    correctAnswer: "'undefined'",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the 'instanceof' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: [
      "Checks if a variable is an instance of a specific class",
      "Performs bitwise OR operation",
      "Checks if a variable is defined",
      "Checks if a variable is null",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Checks if a variable is an instance of a specific class",
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used for bitwise XOR in JavaScript?",
    options: ["&", "|", "^", "~"],
    correctAnswer: "^",
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'typeof true' return in JavaScript?",
    options: ["'boolean'", "'number'", "'string'", "'undefined'"],
    correctAnswer: "'boolean'",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the '<<' operator in JavaScript?",
    options: ["Logical shift left", "Logical shift right", "Bitwise shift left", "Bitwise shift right"],
    correctAnswer: "Bitwise shift left",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the result of the expression 'true && false' in JavaScript?",
    options: ["true", "false", "Error", "Undefined"],
    correctAnswer: "false",
  },
];
module.exports = exprssionsOperators;
